Are you free?
Take your time!
I'm afraid of heights!
It's a fine day!
How's it going?
Never better!
Good to see you!
Come on in!
Have a seat!
Help yourself!
Take your time!
Is this seat taken?
Go ahead!
This seat is taken!
Scoot over a bit!
Got a minute?
Take a look!
What's the hold-up?
Get dressed!
I'm running late!
I gotta go!
Here you are!
Sounds good!
Ready to go?
Wait for me!
Good to go!
Here I am!
I'm here!
What's it called?
Do something!
I can't stand it!
It slipped my mind!
I accidentally forgot!
It happens!
This is a common thing.
What did you say?
You're breaking up!
The signal is bad!
I can't hear you!
Speak up, please!
What day is today?
Today is Sunday.
Today is Monday.
今天是星期一?
See you around!
改天见!
Be right back!
马上回来!
Is it cold outside?
It's chilly out!
What's up?
How are you recently?
Can't complain!
还不错!
Same here!
我也是!
Am I right?
我说的没错吧!
There you go!
你做到了!
Listen up!
听好了!
Think it over!
It's up to you!
有你决定!
Is that clear?
懂了吗?
I'm behind you!
我知你!
Time to go!
该走了!
Come with me!
跟我来!
Have you eaten?
吃过了吗?
Let's grab coffee!
一起去喝咖啡?
My treat!
我请客!
Table for two!
两位用餐!
Long time no see!
Talk to you later!
Sorry to bother you!
抱歉打扰你!
Are you in line?
It sure is!
It's all good!
Check, please!
Let's split the bill!
To-go box, please!
Please pack the boxes for me!
I'm all set!
Catch you later!
回頭見!
How come?
That makes sense!
I'm leaving!
See you then!
You OK?
My fever broke!
Feel better!
感覺好多了!
Get well soon!
Count me in!
算我一個!
I owe you one!
我欠你一次人情!
It's a deal!
一言為定!
That's not fair!
這不公平!
Break a leg!
祝你好運!
Your call!
你決定!
Did you hear me?
你有聽到嗎?
Long story short!
長話短說!
Allow me!
讓我來!
Can I try it on?
可以試穿嗎?
Sure thing!
當然!
Does it fit?
覺得合身嗎?
It doesn't fit!
不合身?
Try a size up!
是大一號!
Give me a break!
饒了我吧!
Neither do I!
我也不是!
I'll take this!
我要這個!
Cash or card?
現金或卡?
I'll pay in cash!
我用現金付!
Please wrap it up!
請幫我包起來!
I need a receipt!
我需要收據!
Can I return this?
可以退貨嗎?
Way to go!
做得好!
It's going to rain!
快下雨了!
What's the plan?
有什麼計劃?
Sort of
有一點
I'm with you!
我同意你!
This is it!
就是這個了!
I'm thrilled!
我超興奮!
Speak of the devil!
說到曹操,曹操就到!
Who is this?
請問你哪位?
Make up your mind!
下定決心吧!
As you wish!
如你所願!
Give it a try!
試試看!
How did it go?
進行得如何?
It really hurts!
真的很痛!
It's killing me!
我受不了!
Thanks a million!
萬分感謝!
We are even!
我們扯平了!
Far from it!
遠非如此!
隨便你!
Whatever you say!
No wonder!
Are you serious?
你是認真的嗎?
Absolutely not!
絕對不行!
Don't get me wrong!
It's nothing!
這沒什麼了!
Don't you see?
I get it!
我明白了!
Are you ready?
準備好了嗎?
The sooner the better!
Can we make it?
來得及嗎?
Don't rush me!
別催我!
We're out of time!
我們沒時間了!
I'm an only child!
For real?
Tindema!
Just joking!
只是開玩笑!
Keep that in mind!
That's all I know!
Stay with me!
待在我身邊?
My phone's dead!
我的手機沒電了!
Charge your phone!
給手機充電!
You don't say!
不會吧!真的假的?
For here or to go?
在這裡吃還是拿走?
Enjoy your meal!
用餐愉快!
工作給我!
我可以!
說來話長!
You're right!
你是對的!
What time is it?
現在幾點了?
Sooner or later?
遲早!
It doesn't work!
怕壞了!
Don't bother!
請別費心!
It's about time!
是時候了!
I'm gonna go!
我要走了!
What's the rush?
急什麼呢?
I messed up!
我搞砸了!
You asked for it!
Fine with me!
I didn't mean it!
I'm mad at myself!
我在生自己的氣!
Give me a hand!
I'm afraid I can't!
I'll fix you up!
Your fly is down!
你的拉鍊沒拉?
I'll check it out!
I slept well!
You speak English well!
That's all I need!
I must do it!
Don't even try it!
What do you mean?
I'll see to it!
It's incredible!
I'm flattered!
What about you?
So far, so good!
Are you awake?
You finally got up!
I'm heading out!
It's pouring!
Get in the car!
Buckle up!
Don't be picky!
Finish your food!
I got a call!
Someone called me!
Who called you?
How much is this?
Any discount?
Too expensive!
Good deal!
Anything else?
That's all!
Just looking!
Next time!
Cash only!
Keep the change!
No need to look for it!
Am I free to go?
Can I go now?
Say again?
Come to the point!
Never give up!
You got this!
You can do it!
Proud of you!
Good for you!
I'm off!
I'll walk you out!
Sleep tight!
Good night!
Drive safely!
Almost there!
I'm getting fat!
I'm on a diet!
I'm sick of it!
It's over now!
I appreciate it!
Thank you!
My pleasure!
Who did it?
No one knows!
Is it yours?
Who told you that?
I slept in!
I missed my alarm!
You look pale!
Are you alright?
I don't feel good!
I'm not feeling well!
I'm dizzy!
Stay calm!
Can I lie down?
I feel nauseous!
I'm fine!
No worries!
How do I look?
You look sharp!
You're so handsome!
On sale?
I can't afford it!
I see!
I'm on my way!
Come early!
I'll be there soon!
You have my word!
I promise you!
I'm back!
You're doing great!
Ladies first!
After you!
You first!
What's new?
What have you been up to lately?
Same as usual!
Turn it off!
I mean it!
I'm on your side!
I support you!
It's worth a try!
That's not helping!
I won't do it!
Let me guess!
Give me a call!
Call me!
Where were we?
I just woke up!
You'll never know!
I'll get the door!
What you comment?
Nice day, isn't it?
I think so too!
That's crazy!
Watch this!
Come closer!
You scared me!
Let's take a break!
You're the boss!
Let's get started!
I'm here for you!
Thanks anyway!
Not at all!
Let's go!
Have fun!
Hold on!
Just a sec!
It's raining!
Can I have a look?
Let me explain it!
I lost my passport!
My wallet was stolen!
I'm stuffed!
I burped!
How's the weather?
Time to wake up!
Set the alarm!
Are you hungry?
Not yet!
Hi, May!
I'm hungry!
Me too!
Let's eat!
It's on me!
For here!
To go!
Bottoms up!
It tastes strong!
Do you like it?
It's OK!
没关系!
How's your day?
今天过得怎样?
Not bad!
不错!
Have a good day!
祝你今天愉快!
You too!
你也是!
May I be excused?
我可以先离开吗?
Be my guest!
别客气!请便!
You look tired!
你看起来很累!
I'm sleepy!
我困了!
That's not like you!
Leave me alone!
让我静静吧!
Don't bug me!
别烦我!
How old are you?
你几岁了?
That's not the point!
重点不是那个!
What should I do?
I have no idea!
我完全没头绪!
Keep it up!
Try again!
I hope so!
Are you busy now?
你现在忙吗?
I got a text!
我收到简讯了!
The toilet is clogged!
马桶堵住了!
I guess so!
我想是吧!
Leave it to me!
I'll handle it!
我会处理的!
You are so kind!
你人真好!
I'll do my best!
我会尽力!
Let me go!
让我走!
Not now!
现在不行!
Maybe later!
也许晚点吧!
Come quick!
快来!
Right away!
立刻!
All the best!
祝一切顺利!
I'll think about it!
我会考虑一下!
Let's figure it out!
You don't get it!
It's hard to say!
很难说?
I'll do it later!
我等一下做!
Do you hear that?
你有听到吗?
It's fine!
没关系!
All good!
都很好!
What is this?
这是什么?
Watch your step!
小心脚下!
Can you repeat that?
可以再说一次吗?
I don't know!
我不知道!
Where do you live?
你住在哪里?
Never mind!
没关系!算了!
Do you speak English?
你会说英语吗?
Not really!
并不全然是!
What do you think?
你觉得呢?
I'm not interested!
我没兴趣!
I'm thirsty!
我口渴了!
Who are you?
你是谁?
That's right!
没错!
Not much!
没什么!
Your shirt's inside out!
衣服穿反了!
Not a chance!
Need help?
需要帮忙吗?
Help me!
帮帮我!
It's broken!
坏掉了!
Calm down!
冷静!
Take mine!
拿我的吧!
Great idea!
好主意!
You're sweet!
你真贴心!
Watch out!
注意!
Be careful!
小心点!
Call me!
打给我!
Text me!
传讯息给我!
No way!
不可能!
Which way?
走哪边?
Go straight!
直走!
Turn left!
左转!
Turn right!
右转!
How far?
Stop here!
Good job!
Well done!
You're kidding!
No kidding!
说真的!
I can't wait!
我等不及了!
Tell me the truth!
Give me a second!
Where are you from?
It fits!
Too tight!
Too loose!
太松了!
I agree!
我同意!
I disagree!
我不同意!
Who knows?
谁知道?
What's going on?
发生什么事了?
I'm on it!
我马上处理!
Stay focused!
保持专注!
Keep going!
坚持下去!
I'm tired!
我累了!
I need some rest!
我需要休息一下!
What else?
还有其他的吗?
That's all for now!
暂时就这样!
Do you understand?
你明白吗?
I understand!
我明白!
Let's begin!
我们开始吧!
I'm listening!
我在听!
Think twice!
再考虑一下!
Let me see!
让我想想!
Who cares?
谁在乎?
Take it easy!
放轻松!
That's true!
那是真的!
Move on!
继续吧!
Stay here!
留在这里!
I'd rather not!
我宁愿不这么做!
By the way!
顺带一提!
Skip it!
算了!
Answer the phone!
请接电话!
Leave a message!
请留言!
Who's this?
你是哪位?
It's me!
Wrong number!
打错了!
Call back later!
晚点回电!
About when?
大约什么时候?
What does this mean?
这是什么意思?
过来吧!
Get ready!
准备好!
Try your best!
尽力而为!
Miss you!
想你!
Guess what?
Tell me!
Will it rain today?
I'll pick you up!
You're late!
Not again!
又来了!
I was surprised!
我很惊讶!
What's it to you?
关你什么事?
Wait here!
在这等着!
Hang in there!
坚持下去!
Try harder!
再努力点!
Don't move!
别动!
Stay back!
往后退!
Stand by!
准备好!
Keep calm!
保持冷静!
What's your hobby?
你有什么爱好?
Like what?
比如说?
Go away!
走开!
I'm busy!
我很忙!
Look around!
看看周围!
I'm in a hurry!
我在赶时间!
Step aside!
让一让!
Follow me!
跟我来!
Move over!
Almost done!
快完成了!
I give up!
我放弃!
That's enough!
口罗!
Take this!
拿着这个!
Give me five!
我们急讲吧!
I'm ready!
我准备好了!
Come back!
回来!
It's mine!
这是我的!
It's yours!
这是你的!
Show me!
给我看!
Pick one!
选一个!
It's hard!
这很难!
It's easy!
这很简单!
You decide!
你决定!
I'm confused!
我很困惑!
Don't touch!
别碰!
Just go!
走吧!
Don't worry!
别担心!
I promise!
我保证!
I'm lost!
我迷路了!
Don't lie!
别说谎!
Be honest!
要诚实!
No more excuses!
别再辩解了!
It doesn't make sense!
这说不通?
I'm mad!
我生气了!
Come along!
一起来!
Hurry up!
快一点!
Look out!
小心!
Let's talk about it!
我们来谈谈吧!
I made a mistake!
我犯了一个错!
Don't be sad!
别难过!
Stay away from me!
离我远一点!
Step back!
退后一步!
Take care of it!
把这件事处理好!
It's not worth it!
不值得!
Let's keep moving!
我们继续走吧!
Anything you say!
就听你的!
The milk went bad!
牛奶坏掉了!
Since when?
从什么时候开始?
Keep your voice down!
小声一点!
It's not my fault!
不是我的错!
I don't buy it!
我才不信!
I'm sure!
我很确定!
My bad!
我的错!
I'm sorry!
对不起!
No problem!
没问题!
No biggie!
没什么大不了的!
I win!
我赢了!
That's great!
太好了!
You nailed it!
As soon as possible!
越快越好!
You're welcome!
不客气!
Trust me!
相信我!
I swear!
我发誓!
Where is the exit?
Just checking!
只是问问而已!
This soup is hot!
这汤很烫!
Please pass the salt!
请地言过来!
The beef is tender!
牛肉很嫩!
Try some!
尝一些看看!
You bet!
当然!
It's my turn!
That's it!
就这样!
I'm trying!
我在努力!
The water is boiling!
水在煮滚了!
It takes time!
需要一点时间?
My mistake!
是我弄错了!
What for?
为什么?
Get down!
趴下!
Hold on tight!
抓紧!
Hit the road!
该出发了!
Where to?
要去哪?
Fill up the tank!
加满油箱!
Do you have change?
你有零钱吗?
It could be!
可能吧!
Time's up!
时间到了!
Just wait and see!
等着瞧!
The line is busy!
电话忙线中!
One moment!
等一下!
Stop it!
停止!
That's impossible!
难以置信!
Watch your mouth!
注意你的言词!
Say no more!
知道了,不必多说!
Enough is enough!
适可而止!
It's going too far!
这太过分了!
Control yourself!
控制好自己!
Don't let me down!
别让我失望!
You are just in time!
你来的正是时候!
Don't be silly!
别傻了!
Shame on you!
你真丢人!
Got it?
明白了吗?
I have no choice!
我别无选择!
I knew it!
我就知道!
Forget it!
算了吧!
I doubt it!
我才不信!
Change the subject!
换个话题吧!
It depends!
看情况!
Wait a second!
等一下!
Hard to tell!
很难说?
Let me help you!
让我帮你!
Are you sure?
你确定吗?
Good evening!
晚上好!
Take a walk!
Any day will do!
哪一天都可以!
Get up!
起来!
Sit down!
坐下!
Back off!
走开!
Come on!
拜托了!
Cut it out!
别闹了!
Act your age!
成熟点,别置气了!
Be yourself!
做你自己!
I told you so!
我早说过了!
I'm in trouble!
我碰到了麻烦!
Get out of here!
少来,我才不信!
Calm yourself!
冷静点!
No such thing!
没这回事!
You're telling me!
还用你说?
Bite your tongue!
小乌鸦嘴!
Let me try!
让我试试!
Why not?
为什么不?
I'm in.
我加入。
I'm out.
我不参加。
It's been a long time.
好久不见!
Repeat after me!
跟我重复!
Cheer up!
开心点!
Take a breath!
深呼吸!
We are all ears!
我们喜耳恭听!
Believe it or not!
信不信由你?
Don't break the rules!
不要违规!
Stop being rude!
别这么无礼!
Hold your tongue!
保持建模!
I'm sorry I'm late!
对不起我迟到了!
Forgive me!
原谅我!
Where were you?
你跑去哪里了?
I overslept!
我睡过头了!
Nice try!
你想得美!
That's too bad!
太糟糕了!
You can do better!
你可以做得更好!
Go easy on me!
别为难我!
No pain, no gain!
没有付出就没有收获!
Let it be!
顺其自然!
That's life!
这就是人生!
Time will tell!
时间能证明!
I can't help it!
我控制不了!
Go for it!
Your turn!
轮到你了!
Is this correct?
这样对吗?
Of course!
当然!
Not exactly!
不完全是!
I made it!
我做到了!
Congratulations!
恭喜!
Let's take a selfie!
我们自拍一张吧!
Turn off the lights!
关灯吧!
Let's go together!
我们一起走吧!
I'll go with you!
我跟你一起去!
Nice to meet you!
很高兴认识你!
You made my day!
你让我今天好开心!
Thanks for coming!
谢谢你来!
Let's call it a day!
今天就到这吧!
I'm home!
我回来了!
Welcome back!
欢迎回来!
Take care!
保重!
Keep in touch!
保持联系!
You are the best!
你是最棒的!
Time for bed!
该睡觉了!
Sweet dreams!
祝你有个好梦!